A story of wealth, fame, power... and this guy.
Clear History is a comedy, tv movie film directed by Greg Mottola.
Nathan Flomm, in order to avoid the humiliation of having missed out on a hugely
successful business, assumes a new identity on Martha's Vineyard.
He plots revenge when his former business partner moves to the same town.
Nathan Flomm / Rolly DaVore, played by Larry David.
Will Haney, played by Jon Hamm.
Rhonda, played by Kate Hudson.
Jennifer, played by Eva Mendes.
Frank, played by Danny McBride.
Joe Stumpo, played by Michael Keaton.
Going Clear: Scientology and the Prison of Belief is a
2015 documentary film about Scientology.
Directed by Alex Gibney and produced by HBO, it is based on Lawrence Wright's book
Going Clear: Scientology, Hollywood and the Prison of Belief (2013).
The film premiered at the 2015 Sundance Film Festival in Park City, Utah.
It received widespread praise from critics and was nominated for seven
Emmy Awards, winning three, including Best Documentary.
It also received a 2015 Peabody Award and won the award for Best
Documentary Screenplay from the Writers Guild of America.
The film deconstructs Scientology's claims by presenting a
condensed history of the group and its founder, L.
Ron Hubbard, examining how celebrities interact with Scientology, and highlighting the stories of a number
of ex-members and of the abuse and exploitation that they described seeing and experiencing.
The Church of Scientology responded vehemently to the film, complaining to film critics
about their reviews and denouncing the filmmakers and their interviewees.
Going Clear was released in a limited number of theaters on
March 13, 2015, and aired on HBO on March 29, 2015.
It was a major ratings success and by mid-April 2015 had attracted 5.5 million viewers,
making it the second most-watched HBO documentary in the past decade.
It was subsequently released internationally, showing in theaters and on television
despite a sustained campaign by the Church of Scientology to block its release.
The tone is lighthearted.